SEE INTERVIEW #699607
SEE INTERVIEW #47246024
Ms. Sun has brown hair and is not from New Zealand.  Not the witness from the cafe.
Interviewed Ms. Church at 2:04 pm.  Witness stated that she did not see anyone she could identify as the shooter, that she ran away as soon as the shots were fired.

However, she reports seeing the car that fled the scene.  Describes it as a blue Honda, with a license plate that starts with "L337" and ends with "9"
